BGM
Shose.
Um, um...
Uh, okay?
We're doing a play about Hansel and Gretel.
So, it's a play.
So I'm going to dress everyone in different outfits.
A play?
Yes, a play.
We're going to play a song in the play.
You're really doing Hansel and Gretel?
Yes, we are.
A slightly modified version of it.
A modernized version.
Yes, sir.
I'll do it.
Have you read the original Hansel and Gretel?
I have.
Yes, I have.
That's mine, right?
So I'm thinking of playing the part of the confectioner.
We were wondering which of the two would be better.
This one or that one.
Or...
I'm going to go with this cute little outfit.
Isn't the first one a picture of the costume?
No, it's a picture of the outfit.
Like this.
Cookies.
Here's a cake.
And this one.
What's the difference between this and what you showed afterwards?
This is the cute outfit.
And then I put some candy here and there and stuff like that.
Krill and stuff.
It's like an idol-like costume.
Or like full body tights. Or like full body tights.
Like a cookie stuck on a cookie.
Full body tights are fine.
Yes, sir.
Can you do this?
Yes, I can.
I can do a lot.
Here we go.
What do you think?
It's good, isn't it?
Okay, here we go.
Which do you think is better?
Like one day.
I was by the woods.
I was living in the day.
It's like, “I'm happy, I'm happy, I'm happy.
Is that a word you'd use?
Well, yes.
And so the story goes on and on.
Yes.
It's too different from this...
It's too different.
Ah...
Yes, sir.
It's too different.
Oh, but I see... I'll wear it by myself.
I'll choose this one.
So this is the image of five people.
Yes, sir.
I see.
I'll take care of it.
Full body tights.
Yes, sir.
Like full-body tights.
Full-body tights.
No, yes.
Full-body tights. full-length tights
yes
what kind of snacks do you like?
Yes, sir
I want a doughnut.
You want a doughnut?
Yes, sir.
I mean, if that's what you're after.
No, I'd rather have cookies.
No, donuts.
You sure?
Donuts are fine.
Uh...
Okay, donuts.
What kind of doughnut? You want to leave that up to me?
Uh, you know, just something cute.
The cuter the better.
Cute donuts.
Wait a minute.
Oh, like this.
Oh, I like that one. I like that one.
I like this one.
I'll do this.
Yeah, this is good.
I like this one.
This is good.
Can you dance?
What?
I don't think I can dance.
Thank you very much.
And Cara.
This flying guy.
That guy is amazing. He's amazing.
That's great.
Please.
What?
This picture...
Yes.
Oh, wait.
But I just got this, too.
Oh, this just now...
I like it.
Okay.
I don't like it.
Have some!
Sports.
Hey, it's funny!
Is it okay to joke around like this?
What? It's fine.
It's fine.
It's pretty cute.
No, I think it's fine.
What?
Oh, thank you.
I can do it with my shoulder.
Oh, sure, sure.
Shoulder, sure.
Uh, sure, sure, that's fine.
It's just...
It's funny.
That's funny.
It's kind of stupid, isn't it?
No, I like this one.
I like this one.
I think it's good.
Is it good?
Yes, I do.
Yes, I like it.
Oh, wow.Oh, wow!
What kind of fabric is this?
Oh, but it used to be like a stuffed animal fabric.
Oh, wow.
You walk on this?
Yes, it is.
Cute.
Is it cute?
What do you think? I think it's cute. You could walk around in it.
Do you think it's cute?
I don't know, I think it's cute.
It's cute.
I wonder if they'd ask to take a picture with it.
Will they?
Oh, they will.
Will they? Well, I'll just make myself popular.
I'm going to go with the popularity strategy.
I'm looking forward to it.
I can't wait to come.
Yes, sir.
I'll take this one.
Thank you very much.
I'm so happy.
Cute.
Cute?
Yes, it is.
Well, I wasn't sure if it was going to work or not.
I'm really proud of you, SOTY.
I'm going to win for sure.
Oh, really?
I'm going to win!
Yay!
We did it! I did it.
Wait, wait, wait, it's so heavy!
Wait a minute.
Costumes, too.
And the costumes
Costumes.
There's no such thing as a costume anymore!
Excuse me.
Yes, sir.
This is a full-body time.
Thank you very much.
Time for the whole body!
Full-body time.
Change.
So we're going on tour.
What's going to happen?
One full-body time, just wear it for a little bit.
Okay. Okay.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Just like now.
It's so dusty.
Wait, it's so cute.
This is SOTY.
That's great.
Yes, it is.
Amazing.
You're gonna make it.
That's amazing.
You can make anything!
That's great.
I made it, I made it, I wore it.
How was it?
It was good.Good.
It's likely to be in a thousand days.
Hey, sure.
I'll take this home with me.
If you put it around the north...
You can sleep on it.
Thank you.
Hey, hey, hey,
They're cute.
Shoes.
You get these a lot, don't you?
Hey.
Retired casual.
It fits.
Your mouth is in trouble.
I'll dance with it.
Hey.
Hands. Hands.
Hey,
Echo this song far and wide.
Per.
It's true.
That's great.
It's perfect.
Is it pretty?
Thank you very much.
It's really cute.
It's too cute.
Oh, wow.
Which one do you like better?
Hey.
When you move,
It's like..,
It's like we're gonna collide.
You don't know the width of a bump. You don't know the width of a bump.
Not yet.
Comfortable.
Can you sleep like this?
If I move like this..,
I don't need a neck brace.
Like a hot dog.
Like this.
Okay.
Mix it like this.
It's a little bit thicker.
I thought it was too genius to be vertical.
Vertical is genius.
It looks like this side.
It's true.
Maoni-chan?
Oh, I'm so proud of you.
I wonder how she'll pose.
What's what?
They'll show us. He shows us so much.
It's too much. Thank you very much.
You look better in the front.
Can you show me the back and skip the front?
You can't do that?
It's so much fun.
I want to be number one.
I'll do my best.
Thanks for your hard work.
You want to hit from the bottom? Oh, no.
What do you think?
Still the same... No.1 impact.
No impact. Impact.
I think you have to buy these things based on impact.
Yes, please.
Today, Upstar. Interesting.Today, upstar. Interesting.
It sure looks like Upstar is going to sell.
Upstar.
But if you do it this way, it's Upstar.
Do it this way. Do it like this.
Which hand is better? This one.
I don't know what the right answer is.
What should I do?
Should I smile? I don't know.
No, uh...
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I think it's fine either way.
Either way is fine.
I think it's okay to be the other way around.
Okay.
Can you jump?
Jump. Here we go. Ready?
Spread your hands. Spread your hands.
What?
Spread your hands.
Spread your hands. Ready.
How's it going?
How is it?
Yes, I'm good.
Thank you very much.
It's a little hard to hear, isn't it?
Also, I don't know what it feels like.
I can't feel it.
Hoi, hoi, hoi.
It's, uh, winding.
Oh, yes, yes. It's a little, you know, cute.
Fluffy. Like a girly girl.
I had my hair done.
Thank you very much.
Oh, I'm glad to hear that.Oh, I'm glad to hear that.
I'm glad.
This, this, I feel like I'm popular.
Every time I see them, they touch it.
Maybe it's a hit with the family crowd? Maybe.
I'm going to try my best to be popular with the little kids today, especially with the families.
Do you want to win the top prize or something?
Yes, that's right.
Please do.
How's it going?
Well, it's already going well. I think we are off to a good start, just as I thought we would be.
Aisho, good point.
I mean, this doughnut is so cute, and the shape of the doughnut, and the pink color of the doughnut,
And this donut is pink, but there is colorful spray on it.
This is a cute point. Yes, it's cute.
And also, because it's soft and fluffy, people who pass by will ruffle it up, so that's another point that makes me happy.
It's perfect, it's perfect, it's perfect.
It's perfect. When I was thinking about the design, I didn't have the idea of putting my head here first.
Then, SOTY came up with the idea, and I thought, “Is he a genius? I was like, “You're a genius.
That's what I thought.
I was planning to put a doughnut here, a small body doughnut here, but I was amazed that you could put a head here.
It's amazing that they can make anything.
I was really impressed by your genius.
Yes, just by looking at the costumes, I am sure that they will make you feel happy and wonderful. I am sure that anyone who comes to this performance will feel happy and wanderlust.
I want to win the first place.
I want to win first place, everyone.
Thank you very much.